# Hi! I'm Juan Cruz

I am 23 years old, I have a Bachelor's degree on Advertisement in Universidad Siglo 21. I am a very curious person and I am always looking to learn skills or about new topics. I have facility in the use of digital tools for the creation of designs and multimedia files. I am passionate about visual arts, mainly graphic design and video editing.

# Contact

+386 70 252 088 juancruzolmosv@gmail.com

# **Education**

#### 2019/2023

Bachelor of Advertisement - Universidad Siglo 21 2017

Graduate on Visual Arts - Colegio Jesus María

#### Certifications

Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Powerpoint) Adobe (Photoshop, Dreamweaver) Corel (DRAW).

First Certificate Exam (B2) - University of Cambridge

# **Skills**

Visual arts and communication

### Adobe Suite

Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects, Premiere Pro, Lightroom, XD and InDesign

**UX/UI Design** 

**FrontEnd** 

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript

Davinci Resolve (Video Editing)

# Work Experience

#### December 2022 - April 2023

## **Graphic Designer - Weiv**

Conceptualized and created visual designs that effectively communicated clients message and brands identities.

#### December 2022 - March 2023

## **Graphic Designer (Freelance) - Gohan House**

Created high-quality designs that were visually appealing and consistent with clients brand guidelines for social media posts

# May 2022 - August 2022

## **Graphic Designer (Freelance) - newEra Battles**

Designed the brand identity and create a range of print and digital materials such as brochures, flyers, social media graphics, and more.

# June 2021 - August 2021

## **Graphic Designer - Elephant Digital Group**

Prepared and delivered final design files and videos in various formats for different brands.

#### January 2021 - June 2021

#### **Account Executive - Agencia Move**

Managed and grew relationships with clients to ensure their satisfaction and achieve business goals. Collaborated with other team members to develop and implement effective marketing strategies and campaigns.

Acted as a primary point of contact for clients, responding to inquiries and providing support as needed.